Look, yarn warehouse, it's full of
works.  It was also exciting when the
works arrived and the people who
work here were also a little
worried because what if when I move the
crates I accidentally knock over a work
of art?  Look, I don't know the answer.
But if someone
ruins the artwork in my row when I'm on vacation, we didn't know what to do
there either.  But
how much does the work cost?  Well, they cost 1 10
100. It was like, "Ah, but all this
money here, why don't you put it
in your homes?"  And dad replied with
his normality of the time: they are here
living with us and the works of art
help us to always have the desire to
reinvent the way of weaving
the unweaveable.
How many are there in total?
24,000.
24,000 works.  Damn, but even
more so because actually
eight new ones arrived the other day
because there are donations.  Then
in 2013 all of this became the
Bonotto Foundation to manage all the traffic
because a lot of loans were starting to come in
, museums from all over the world
were starting to come to dad
asking him to borrow works.
Do you have an online archive?  Yes, everything
was on the site.  Dad wanted
the site to be accessible to everyone,
so everyone can go in and see
everything as
free, downloadable, and accessible artistic research.
We get about 10,000 visits
a day, so that's incredible for us
.